Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Good morning Church.
My name is Oksana Ojeba.
I am from Ukraine.
My husband is from Kogi State in Nigeria.
I have been here for 15 years.
When I was in Ukraine and I was 16 years old,
I met my husband in my country, and I saw him as a very handsome man.
Something inside me told me that he was my husband.
I was with him for five years as a friend.
When my husband finished university, he wanted to go back to Nigeria
and I was pregnant.
I begged him to marry me because the child would not be my colour
and if I was not married, no one would like my child.
After my husband married me, I said, 'Thank God'.
When my husband was in my country, he suffered.
No one gave him work; my husband was buying and selling clothes.
He was really suffering.
After I saw that my child was not happy and my husband was suffering because of colour,
I started praying to God that I would be able to bring my husband to Nigeria.
Before we came to Nigeria, my husband was very sick spiritually.
He had another woman who got pregnant for him.
The woman started disturbing him to come to her but I said no, that we should go to Nigeria.
When I got to Nigeria, I was very happy when people welcomed me.
When I got to Nigeria, I was very happy when I, my children and my husband were welcomed.
When I came, I saw that everybody wanted to play with my children.
I saw my husband's eyes became clear and he was very happy.
He was speaking a better language. I was very happy because I saw that he was free.
But later, my husband did not get work again in Nigeria.
After I gave birth to two children here, my husband started going from one woman to another.
When I saw that my husband was not happy and no one was helping him, I looked for help.
I saw a canteen woman who helped me with a job and paid me 7,000 naira.
I was washing plates and serving people.
I prayed to God to give me another job and then someone asked me to help train chicken.
I got paid 2,000 or 3,000 naira.
Nobody helped me. My daughter was hungry to the extent that she would
use a razor blade, cut herself and write on her body, 'I hate you'.
Sometimes, I would peel cassava and somebody would help me to fry gari.
I would cook and eat Nigerian food.
I want to get help from someone for my husband.
I want my husband to be happy and smile.
Please, Man of God, help my husband!
I want to thank God because when I came to The SCOAN, I had only 20,000 naira.
I did not think about where I would stay in a hotel; I only wanted to come to the church.
I asked the ushers to help me.
T.B. Joshua paid for my hotel and feeding.
I want to thank T.B. Joshua so much
because I did not sleep on the streets but in a hotel.
Mrs Oksana Ojeba - Shares Life Experience
This is my husband - my darling, my angel.
If it was not for my husband, I would not understand who God is.
He was the one who brought me to God.
This is me.
This is my son who is 26 years old.
This is me during our wedding.
So we can see in the photograph - she said this was her wedding day
and we can see her husband standing behind her.
She said that her husband is her darling husband, her angel
and she thanks God that despite the condition they are in,
he has stayed with her; they have been together and he is a loving husband to her.
These are my daughters.
This is my son.
We can see there her son - her first son on the screen there.
All of them have been living in this suffering condition for many years.
But as she has come here today to The SCOAN,
we truly believe, Madam, that your needs will be met in Christ Jesus.
STANDARD FOR LIFE
My name is Oksana Ojeba.
I am from Ukraine.
The problem that brought me here was poverty.
I got married in my country, Ukraine, to my husband who is a Nigerian.
My husband was at University in Ukraine.
When he finished university, he did not find a job.
He was selling clothes, and it was not easy for him.
I came to Nigeria and gave birth to two more children.
I could not get a job and was suffering.
I was moving up and down, begging for my children and my husband but nobody helped.
I came to The SCOAN for God to help me.
On behalf of Prophet T.B. Joshua and the Emmanuel TV partners,
we are here to present to you the sum of 300,000 naira
to take care of yourself, your husband and your children.
Mrs Oksana Ojeba receives 300,000 naira from the Emmanuel TV partners
and Prophet T.B. Joshua to take her back home and enable her and her husband
to forget the struggles of the past and start a new life in Christ.
Thank you so much, T.B. Joshua.
I thank the God of T.B. Joshua for not forgetting me and for hearing my prayers.
I want to use this money for business because this money is blessed.
I believe that with this money, my life will be better.
I will come back to give a testimony with my family.
Amen. We thank God Almighty for your life and we encourage you
you are blessed today by the Word of God
so make the Word of God the standard for your life.
Jesus Christ does not promise to keep us away from trials, tests or poverty,
but He promised to be with us and to see us through.
As God Almighty has shown you that at last, the end to your poverty has come,
the end to your problem has come,
it is time for you to live in the light of your testimony in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Thank you, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Thank you, Emmanuel TV.